let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In what country did the first Starbucks open outside of North America?",
    answer: "Japan",
    options: [
      "England",
      "Uruguay",
      "Japan",
      "Sweden"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who composed the 'Moonlight Sonata'?",
    answer: "Ludwig van Beethoven",
    options: [
      "Ludwig van Beethoven",
      "Wolfgang Amadeus",
      "Frédéric Chopin",
      "Johann Sebastian Bach"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In a website browser address bar, what does “www” stand for? ",
    answer: "World Wide Web",
    options: [
      "World Wide Win",
      "We Will Win",
      "World Wide Website",
      "World Wide Web"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who, in 1903, was the first woman to win a Nobel Prize?",
    answer: "Marie Curie",
    options: [
      "Leymah Gbowee",
      "Ellen Johnson Sirleaf",
      "Marie Curie",
      "Tawakkol Karman"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What year did the Berlin Wall fall?",
    answer: "1989",
    options: [
      "1990",
      "1989",
      "1986",
      "1999"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What element does the chemical symbol Au stand for?",
    answer: "Gold",
    options: [
      "Silver",
      "Platinum",
      "Gold",
      "Titanium"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the sign directly opposite Scorpio in the zodiac?",
    answer: "Taurus",
    options: [
      "Leo",
      "Aries",
      "Scorpio",
      "Taurus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: [
      "Mars",
      "Jupiter",
      "Mercury",
      "Pluto"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the highest-grossing Broadway show of all time?",
    answer: "The Lion King",
    options: [
      "Wicked",
      "Hamilton",
      "The Lion King",
      "Aladdin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Gareth Bale plays for which country?",
    answer: "Wales",
    options: [
      "Wales",
      "Sweden",
      "Finland",
      "Scotland"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Complete the name of this former Premier League team. Bolton _____",
    answer: "Wanderers",
    options: [
      "County",
      "Vale",
      "Wanderers",
      "City"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "David Beckham left Manchester United in 2003 to join which Spanish team?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Real Madrid",
      "Valencia",
      "Getafe"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Former Arsenal manager Arsene Wenger is from which country?",
    answer: "France",
    options: [
      "Italy",
      "Portugal",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "David Beckham played for which MLS team in the United States?",
    answer: "LA Galaxy",
    options: [
      "Atalanta United",
      "Inter Miami",
      "LA Galaxy",
      "Orlando City"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The city of Liverpool has two clubs in the Premier League - Liverpool & which other?",
    answer: "Everton",
    options: [
      "West Ham",
      "Crystal Palace",
      "Sheffield United",
      "Everton"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Steven Gerrard & Wayne Rooney are both from which English city?",
    answer: "Liverpool",
    options: [
      "Manchester",
      "Liverpool",
      "Swansea",
      "Bristol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Fulham Football Club are situated in which English city?",
    answer: "London",
    options: [
      "Birmingham",
      "Leicester",
      "London",
      "Coventry"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "As of 2020, which of these teams have been relegated the most times from the Premier League?",
    answer: "Norwich City",
    options: [
      "Sunderland",
      "West Brom",
      "Norwich City",
      "Hull City"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "What type of weaponry features on the Arsenal club badge?",
    answer: "Cannon",
    options: [
      "Machine Gun",
      "Dagger",
      "Shotgun",
      "Cannon"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "What is the nickname of Arsenal Football Club?",
    answer: "The Gunners",
    options: [
      "The Gooners",
      "The Gunners",
      "The Guns",
      "The Gunner Boys"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Which of these is a famous stand at Liverpool's Anfield stadium?",
    answer: "The Kop",
    options: [
      "The Kopp",
      "The Cop",
      "The Kops",
      "The Kop"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Which Merseyside club play at Goodison Park?",
    answer: "Everton",
    options: [
      "Everton",
      "Tranmere",
      "Southport",
      "Pilkington"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "What did Eric Cantona do in 1995 that earned him a 9 month ban from football?",
    answer: "Kung-fu kicked an opposing fan during a game",
    options: [
      "Took off his clothes during the game",
      "Punched the referee in the face",
      "Kung-fu kicked an opposing fan during a game",
      "Threw things into the crowd"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "What type of animal features on the Chelsea club badge?",
    answer: "Lion",
    options: [
      "Tiger",
      "Lion",
      "Jaguar",
      "Panther"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Which team did Thiago Alcantara sign for in the summer of 2020?",
    answer: "Liverpool",
    options: [
      "Bayern Munich",
      "Barcelona",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Liverpool"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Who is the leading goal scorer in La Liga history?",
    answer: "Lionel Messi",
    options: [
      "Telmo Zarra",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Hugo Sanchez"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Who won La Liga Best Player award 2015/2016?",
    answer: "Antonio Griezmann",
    options: [
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Antonio Griezmann",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Luis Suarez"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Which club has the highest number of trophies in spain?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Barcelona",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Espanyol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Messi scored his first ever hat trick against which spanish club?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Betis",
      "Getafe",
      "Athletic Bilbao",
      "Real Madrid"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "2010 Fifa World Cup best player named Diego Forlan who played which spanish clubs?",
    answer: "Villareal and Atletico Madrid",
    options: [
      "Villareal and Atletico Madrid",
      "Villareal and Sevilla",
      "Real Madrid and Real Sociedad",
      "Atletico Madrid and Real Betis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Which year did Messi scored his first ever hat trick against Real Madrid?",
    answer: "2007",
    options: [
      "2009",
      "2008",
      "2007",
      "2010"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question: "Which is the oldest club in spain?",
    answer: "Sevilla",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Sevilla",
      "Barcelona",
      "Athletic Club"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question: "Who has won the most number of 'Zamora Trophy' by keeping highest amount of clean sheets in La Liga history?",
    answer: "Jan Oblak",
    options: [
      "Iker Casillas",
      "Victor Valdes",
      "Mark-Andre ter Stegen",
      "Jan Oblak"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question: "Which stadium in spain has the highest seating capacity with 99,354 seats?",
    answer: "Camp Nou",
    options: [
      "Estadio Vicente Calderon",
      "Estadio Santiago Bernabeu",
      "Camp Nou",
      "RCDE Stadium"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "Who was the first Real Madrid's manager?",
    answer: "Arthur Johnson",
    options: [
      "Juande Ramos",
      "Vicente del Bosque",
      "Fabio Capello",
      "Arthur Johnson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 36,
    question: "AC Milan was founded in December 1899. Which English city were the club's founders from?",
    answer: "Nottingham",
    options: [
      "Nottingham",
      "Birmingham",
      "Bergamo",
      "Venice"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Which club, famous for their purple shirts, were the first-ever winners of the European Cup Winners' Cup in 1961?",
    answer: "Fiorentina",
    options: [
      "Juventus",
      "Fiorentina",
      "Roma",
      "Napoli"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "In which year did AC Milan win their first Campionato?",
    answer: "1901",
    options: [
      "1901", 
      "1900",
      "1902",
      "1905"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "Who was AC Milan's captain in the 2003-04 season?",
    answer: "Paolo Maldini",
    options: [
      "Roberto Antonelli", 
      "Frank Baresi",
      "Caesar Maldini",
      "Paolo Maldini"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Which striker was topscorer three times in the 90s, when he played for Lazio?",
    answer: "Giuseppe Signori",
    options: [
      "Gabriel Batistuta", 
      "Giuseppe Signori",
      "Roberto Baggio",
      "Ciro Immobile"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 41,
    question: "Against which Spanish side did Juventus win the UEFA Cup in 1977?",
    answer: "Athletico Bilbao",
    options: [
      "Osasuna", 
      "Sevilla",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Athletico Bilbao"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 42,
    question: "The first FIFA World Cup tournament was held in",
    answer: "1930",
    options: [
      "1930", 
      "1929",
      "1940",
      "1928"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 43,
    question: "Which country became the first from Africa to compete at a World Cup finals?",
    answer: "Egypt",
    options: [
      "Egypt", 
      "Morocco",
      "Tunisia",
      "Algeria"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 44,
    question: "Which country was the first to win two World Cups?",
    answer: "Italy",
    options: [
      "Brazil", 
      "Scotland",
      "Italy",
      "Germany"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 45,
    question: "No country outside of Europe or South America has ever won the men’s World Cup. True or False?",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "Neither", 
      "Both",
      "False",
      "True"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 46,
    question: "What was bizarre about Australia’s qualification for the 1998 World Cup?",
    answer: "They were unbeaten but still didn’t qualify for the tournament",
    options: [
      "They competed with the CONMEBOL nations for a place", 
      "They had four different managers",
      "They were unbeaten but still didn’t qualify for the tournament",
      "None of their starting XI against Fiji was born in Australia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 47,
    question: "Who won the top scorer title at the tournament on Mexican soil in 1986?",
    answer: "Gary Lineker",
    options: [
      "Diego Maradona", 
      "Gary Lineker",
      "Michel Platini",
      "Zico"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 48,
    question: "This is the first tournament for both Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo. How many goals did they score each (2006)?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "4", 
      "6",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 49,
    question: "Who won the Best Young Player award in 2014?",
    answer: "Paul Pogba",
    options: [
      "Memphis Depay", 
      "James Rodriguez",
      "Paul Pogba",
      "Luke Shaw"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 50,
    question: "The 2018 tournament is a record-setting tournament for the number of-",
    answer: "Most own goals",
    options: [
      "Most own goals", 
      "Most goals",
      "Most hat-tricks",
      "Most red cards"
    ]
  },
    
];

